A Guide to the Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection, 1998-2008
Thomas Balch Library
- (SERIES 2: Event Photographs)
  - 1
    - March 9 2009 [CD 2496], 03/09/2009
    - March 9 2009 [CD 2497], 03/09/2009
    - Leesburg & Morven Park 4-20-2007 [CD 009835], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Battlefield Parkway 4-20-2007 [CD 009831], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA & Hospital 4-20-2007 [CD 009834], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-7-2007 [CD 00035927], 05/07/2007
    - 5-7-2007 Leesburg, VA Town [CD 001264], 05/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-7-2007 Battlefield Parkway Town [CD 00035929], 05/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-19-2007 [CD 002496], 05/19/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Battlefield Parkway 5-19-2007 [CD 002497], 05/19/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-19-2007 The Circle [CD 002495], 05/19/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Carr Property 6-7-2007 [CD 003770], 06/07/2007
    - Hospital - Cornwall Site 6-7-2007 Leesburg, VA [CD 003754], 06/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA - Air Photos taken 6-7-2007 [CD 003748], 06/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 6-21-2007 [CD 004809], 06/21/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 6-21-2007 [CD 004808], 06/21/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 6-21-2007 [CD 004807], 06/21/2007
    - Cornwall Pavilion LP Leesburg, VA Site 6-21-2007 [CD 004811], 06/21/2007
    - Landsdown [sic] & Shopping Center [CD 005730], 07/02/2007
    - Cornwall Pavilion LP Leesburg, VA 7-2-2007 [CD 005731], 07/02/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Battlefield Parkway 7-2-2007 [folder entry: 18 photos; CD 005732], 07/02/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 7-2-2007 [CD 005733], 07/02/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Hospital Cornwall Site 7-14-2007 [CD 006709], 07/14/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 7-14-2007 [CD 006707], 07/14/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Air Phto's 7-14-2007 [CD 006708], 07/14/2007
    - Top 1st 6 pictures - are of Winchester VA, Row 2-3 & 4 - Leevurg VA, Rivercreek & Rt 7 7-14-2007 [CD 006705], 07/14/2007
    - 1-11 Berryville, VA, 12-24 Leesburg, VA 8-10-2007 Leesburg, VA [CD 009957], 08/10/2007
    - Leesburg, VA - Business Park Goose Creek Area 8-14-2007 [CD 009952], 08/10/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 8-14-2007 [CD 009956], 08/10/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Hospital 8-14-2007 [CD 009953], 08/10/2007
    - Cornwall Pavilion LP, Leesburg, VA Hospital 8-14-2007 [CD 009954], 08/10/2007
    - Leesburg VA 8-14-2007 [CD 009963], 08/10/2007
    - Leesburg - Inova Hospital & Cornwall Pavilion LP #17-24 Purcellville Med Center 9-3-2007 [folder entry: 14 photos; CD 1834-A], 09/03/2007
    - Leesburg VA - Battlefield - River Creek & Rt 7 9-3-2007 [CD 1836-A], 09/03/2007
    - Leesburg VA 9-3-2007 [CD 1835-A], 09/03/2007
    - Hospital Cornwall - Leesburg VA 9-19-2007 [CD 2954-A], 09/19/2007
    - Leesburg VA Air Downtown 9-19-2007 [CD 2953-A], 09/19/2007
    - Leesburg VA Downtown #2 9-19-2007 [CD 2946-A], 09/19/2007
    - Kincaid Farm Leesburg VA 9-19-2007 [CD 2952-A], 09/19/2007
    - Air Photo's Take 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA Battlefield Parkway [CD 2947-A], 09/19/2007
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos 9-19-2007 [CD 2948-A], 09/19/2007
  - 2
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos 10-14-2007 [CD 4404-A], 10/14/2007
    - Leesburg VA 10-14-2007 [CD 4410-A], 10/14/2007
    - Inova Hospital Leesburg VA 3-17-2008 [CD 3883-A], 03/17/2008
    - Town of Leesburg VA Air Photos 3-17-2008 [CD 3884-A], 03/17/2008
    - Town - Leesburg VA Air Photos 3-17-2008 [3886-A], 03/17/2008
    - Air Photo's of Leesburg VA taken 3-17-2008 [CD 3885-A], 03/17/2008
    - Leesburg VA - Rt 7 & River Creek Interchange Taken 6-12-2008 #1 [CD 7895-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos #2 taken 6-12-2008 [CD 7908-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos #3 taken 6-12-2008 [CD 7907-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Airport Area Air Photos taken 6-12-2008 #4 [CD 7897-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos taken 6-12-2008 Battlefield Pk #5 [CD 7899-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos taken 6-12-2008 #6 [CD 7901-A], 06/12/2008
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos taken 6-12-2008 #7 Airport [CD 7902-A]
    - Leesburg VA Air Photos Hospital - Rust taken 6-12-2008 #8 [CD 7904-A], 06/12/2008
    - Air Photo's - Leesburg, VA taken 8-20-2008 #1 [CD 2184-A], 08/20/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 8-20-2008 #2 [CD 2187-A], 08/20/2008
    - Air Photo's - Leesburg, VA taken 8-20-2008 #3 [CD 2182-A], 08/20/2008
    - Air Photo's - Leesburg, VA taken 8-20-2008 #4 [CD 2179-A], 08/20/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #1 [CD 6962-A], 11/07/2008
    - [11-7-2008 #2, CD 6967-A], 11/07/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #3 [CD 6966-A], 11/07/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #4 [CD 6963-A], 11/07/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #5 [CD 6964-A], 11/07/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #6 [CD 6968-A], 11/07/2008
    - Air Photo's - Town of Leesburg, VA taken 11-7-2008 #7 [CD 6965-A], 11/07/2008